Finding Aid to the Save the Redwoods League photograph collection. 1885-2014
The Bancroft Library
- Series 2: Humboldt County Photographic Survey., 1900-circa 1965, bulk 1920s-1930s; cartons 9-10; NEG boxes 3, 5; NNEG boxes 3-4,6-9.
  - Humboldt redwoods (general)., circa 1920?-1936 (Carton 10)
    2 related negatives of Prairie Creek Redwoods area after fire (survey numbers 9145, 9146) removed to NEG box 5. 5 related negatives (3 of redwood trees by H.C. Tibbitts, survey numbers 9141a-c; 2 of park administration house) removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Photographs in the Prairie Creek Gold Bluffs to the divide west of Prairie Creek [album]., 1931-1946 (Carton 10)
    Notebook type album that has been disbound and foldered. Includes Carothers property near Del Norte County line, lagoon at Lower Bluff Mine in the Gold Bluff west of Prairie Creek, abandoned Lower Bluff Mine, old roads through Marks Timber, Roosevelt elk, and Boyes Prairie area.
    Includes photographs by Newton B. Drury, Paul Clary, Moulin Studios, Warden C.L. Milne, E.P. French and Ashley C. Browne
    9200A-9239 (Save the Redwoods League numbering scheme).
  - Devastation views [album]., circa 1925-1965 (bulk circa 1925-1936) (Carton 10)
    Disbound album of landscapes, roads, road construction and devastation from highway realignment, buildings, logging and lumbering operations in Humboldt County, and a few in Mendocino County. Bulk are snapshots. Locations are mainly along the Redwood Highway. Includes Pepperwood, Red Crest, Eel River, Englewood, Dyerville, Weott, Perrott property, Burlington, Myers, auto camp at Meyers, Tuttle property, Miranda, Baker property, Sylvandale, Garberville, Dean property, Caton and Tooby property, Chandler Smith property, Fish Creek Grove, Hurlbutt property, North Dyerville Flat, Samoa, Scotia, Percy Brown's Mill, Bull Creek, and Sage Unit Number 1.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, H.C. Tibbitts, Freeman Art Co., Anne Bancroft, and David Swanlund.
    12001-12173 (Save the Redwoods League numbering scheme).
    2 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 8.
  - South Fork of Eel River., 1925-1936, undated (Carton 10)
    Unnumbered, loose photographs found with the survey photographs. Bulk are in Humboldt County, but a few are identified as Mendocino County. Photographs are not numbered.
    Includes photographs by Gabriel Moulin, H.S. Lawton, Tibbitts, E.R. Freeman, E.P. French and Martin.
    1 related negative removed to NNEG box 6. 1 related negative removed to NNEG box 4.
  - Eel River., 1900-1935, undated (Carton 10)
    Unnumbered, loose photographs found with the survey photographs. Includes Scotia Bluffs and Pacific Lumber Company Railroad.
    Includes photographs by Gabriel Moulin, H.S. Lawton, Tibbitts, Freeman Art Company, Kenny Kilburn, Martin and Frank Kuykendall.
- Series 3: Albums (boxed)., circa 1915-1999; ALB volumes 1, 4-10; fALB volumes 2, 3; PIC boxes 1-2, B box 2; NEG box 2
  Arranged chronologically.
  Albums created or collected by Save-the-Redwoods League staff. The bulk of the albums are related to a theme, from trips documenting various redwood forest locations and areas of proposed land acquisition, to tributes and League events. Of note is a study on problems of U.S. Highway 101 widening and re-alignment.
  Thin notebook type albums that were boxed together by Save the Redwoods League staff have been moved to the Vertical Files, and filed by subject.
  - Untitled album with photographs of redwoods trees., circa 1915?; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.1; 32 photographs 17 x 26 x 3.5 cm (Volume 1 (ALB))
    Includes automobiles and horse-drawn buggies on roads in the redwoods, Giant Tree and Flat Iron Tree.
    Album received by Save the Redwoods League, May 13, 1963, from Mr. Heinze, Div. of B. and P. Signed on inside cover: A.D. Pettingill.
  - Save the Redwoods., Prior to 1918; Tibbitts, H. C.; BANC PIC 2006.030--fALB v.2; 22 photographs 30 x 29 x 2 cm (Volume 2 (fALB))
    Includes redwood forests in and near Englevale, Dyerville, Pepperwood, Eureka and Samoa in Humboldt County; Camp Grant, the Lizard Tree, automobiles on the state highway, Eel River, men felling a tree and redwood lumber and saw mill in Scotia.
    - State Highway, Humboldt County, Calif., 1918 or prior; Tibbitts, H. C.; BANC PIC 2006.030--fALB v.2; 1 photograph
      Two automobiles on a road through a redwood forest.
      Number on back of album page: 27381.
    - Camp Grant near Dyerville, Humboldt County., 1918 or prior; Tibbitts, H. C.; BANC PIC 2006.030--fALB v.2; 1 photograph 1 photograph
      Wooden fence at edge of redwood grove.
      Number on back of album page: 16712.
      Coast redwood -- California -- Pictorial works; Humboldt County (Calif.)
  - Save the Redwoods League Office File Album, Photographic Studies., 1923; Tibbitts, H. C.; BANC PIC 2006.030--fALB v.3; 73 photographs 26 x 35 x 6 cm (Volume 3 (fALB))
    Redwood grove and river views in Northern California. Includes Russ Grove, Felton Grove, Bolling Grove, Richardson's Grove, Stephen's Grove, Phillipsville Grove, Eel River, Klamath River, Stone Lagoon, whaling station at Trinidad, James Irvine Tree, road near Scotia, Lane's auto park, bridge at Fernbridge Station, and bridge at Garberville. One loose photo print by Freeman Art Co. of Bolling Grove in front of album.
  - Views of State Highway U.S. 101 Humboldt Redwoods State Park Illustrating Problems in Highway Widening and Re-Alignment (volumes 1- 3)., 1937; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC (Pic boxes 1-2)
    Three albums prepared by California State Parks Commission, with cooperation of United States Department of Interior, National Park Service. Includes maps showing locations of views.
    Volume 1: photos 1-34
    Volume 2: photos 35- 77
    Volume 3: photos 78-110
    Volumes were received by the Bancroft Library in the form of spiral notebooks. Library staff disbound the notebooks and foldered the pages for conservation purposes. Duplicate volumes contain a few different images. Duplicate of volume 1 includes additional loose photographs.
    1 matching negative from volume 1, page 27 removed to NNEG box 3 (with Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Highway Survey negatives.)
  - Save the Redwoods League Acquisitions Program for Four Northern Projects., circa 1963-1967; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.4; 59 photographs 29 x 26 x 4.5 cm (3 ring binder) (Volume 4 (ALB))
    Black and white and color photographs by Howard King, Moulin Studios, David Swanlund, Doug Yule of four state parks in Northern California.
    1. Humboldt Redwoods State Park. Includes Bull Creek watershed, Pepperwood Flat, Avenue of the Giants, California Federation of Women's Clubs Grove and Eel River.
    2. Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park. Includes Fern Canyon, Gold Bluffs Beach, Prairie Creek, Redwood Creek, National Council of State Garden Clubs Grove and Willits Grove.
    3. Del Norte Coast Redwoods. Includes Del Norte Coast and rhododendron.
    4. Jedediah Smith State Park. Includes former Simpson Timber Company land, Mill Creek, Howland Hill Road, Old Stage Coach Road, Metcalf Grove and Stout Tree.
  - Martin Litton Photographs., 1964-1965; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.5; 87 photographs 34 x 31 x 5 cm (3 ring binder) (Volume 5 (ALB))
    Photographs by Martin Litton of ground level and aerial views of redwood forests, and land after logging clear cut, divided into four regions:
    1. Redwood Creek watershed area, which includes Arcata Redwood Company land
    2. Little Lost Man Creek watershed area, which includes C. Thomas land and Berry Glen cut.
    3. Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park area, which includes clear cut logging on Arcata Redwood Company land, Gold Bluffs Road and freeway construction.
    4. Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park area, which includes adopted freeway route (US 199) through the park, Mill Creek Road, Smith River, Simpson Reed Grove, National Tribute Grove, east portal of Ridge Tunnel and clear cut of Malarkey Forest.
    Duplicates photos can be found in the Vertical Files under the subject.
    Matching negatives in NEG box 5.
  - In the Temple of God - Sanctuary: To Newton B. Drury in deepest gratitude and appreciation of his devoted service towards saving the redwoods these fifty years., November 23, 1967; BANC PIC 2006.030--B; 34 x 52 x 4 cm (B box 2)
    Album of photographs, drawings and written tributes to Newton Drury.
  - Seventy-fifth Anniversary Celebrations: Founders Grove and California Federation of Women's Clubs Grove., October 2, 1993; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.6; 86 photographs 27 x 35 x 4.5 cm (Volume 6 (ALB))
    Celebrations held in Humboldt Redwoods State Park. Includes the Founders Tree.
    Matching and related negatives in NEG box 2.
  - Save the Redwoods League Council Meeting and Dedication of Newton B. Drury Parkway, Prairie Creek Redwood State Park., October 3 1993; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.7; 82 photographs 27 x 35 x 4.5 cm (Volume 7 (ALB))
  - Save the Redwoods League tour., August 1998; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.8; 34 x 31 x 5 cm (3 ring binder) (Volume 8 (ALB))
    Includes color snapshots of Marti/Cricket property trip.
  - Save the Redwoods League tours and meetings., 1998-1999; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.9; 34 x 31 x 5 cm (3 ring binder) (Volume 9 (ALB))
    Color snapshots of staff and scenery. Includes Cricket Creek Grove tour, Hartsook planning meeting, Los Angeles member event, San Francisco reception, major donor luncheon.
  - Save the Redwoods League tours and meetings., 1999; BANC PIC 2006.030--ALB v.10; 34 x 31 x 5 cm (3 ring binder) (Volume 10 (ALB))
    Color snapshots of staff and scenery. Includes unidentified luncheon, and an annual council meeting.
    Related panoramic photo removed to A box 1, folder 6.
- Series 4: Postcards., circa 1920-1993; carton 8; NNEG box 6
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, with miscellaneous scenes at the end of the list.
  Commercially produced and real photo postcards, the bulk of which are of redwood trees, parks and other scenes in Northern California.
  Some postcards were made for Save the Redwoods League from League photographs.
  - Big Basin Redwoods State Park (Santa Cruz County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards.
  - Bohemian Grove (Sonoma County). (Carton 8)
  - Crescent City. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Knapp Hospital, lighthouse and breakwater.
  - Del Norte Coast Redwoods State Park. (Carton 8)
  - Drive thru trees. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Chandiler Tree at Leggett, and Shrine Tree at Myer Flat.
  - Eel River (Mendocino County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes South Fork of Eel River, the Redwood Highway, Eel River at Benbow and Coolidge Redwood Park.
  - Giant Redwood Park (Del Norte County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes people standing next to redwood trees.
  - Henry Cowell Redwoods State Park (Santa Cruz County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes General Freemont, Roosevelt, Giant, Jumbo, Big Crater and Jeter Trees, largest card receiver, club house and visitors.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Avenue of the Giants, Founder's Tree, Bull Creek Flat and Pepperwood Flat.
    1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park (Del Norte County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Boy Scouts in front of the Boy Scout Tree, Stout Memorial Grove, Mr. and Mrs. Jesse H. Metcalf Memorial Grove, and Smith River.
  - Lane's Redwood Flat (Mendocino County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes American Green Cross Tree, Redwood Highway, Octopus Tree and campsite under the trees.
  - Lilley Redwood Park (Mendocino County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Fraternal Monarch, or Quadruped, redwood tree house and curio shop interior.
  - Logging. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes people posed in the cut of a redwood tree.
  - Montgomery Woods State Natural Reserve (Mendocino County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Montgomery Grove.
  - Muir Woods National Monument (Marin County). (Carton 8)
  - Petrified Forest, Calistoga (Sonoma County). (Carton 8)
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park (Humboldt County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Elk Tree, Fern Canyon, National Council of State Garden Clubs Grove, Robert and Leona Train Rienow Redwood Grove, John L. Senior Grove and Gold Bluffs Beach.
  - Redwood Highway. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Clam Beach, bridge over the Van Duzen River, Douglas Memorial Bridge, switchbacks at Grant Pass in Oregon, and roadside attractions.
  - Redwood trees. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Bulk are general images of redwood groves. Includes Grizzly Giant, tree in Mariposa Grove; General Sherman, tree in Sequoia and King's Canyon National Park; redwood tree in Coolidge (Underwood) Park; unidentified ceremony in a redwood grove; Sequoia Park in Eureka; groves along the Redwood Highway.
  - Richardson Grove State Park (Humboldt County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Richardson Grove, beach on the Eel River, campsites, store at Devoy Grove and cross sections of redwood trees.
  - Russian River (Sonoma County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes beach scenes at Sully's, Monte Rio.
  - Smith River (Del Norte County). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Hiouchia Bridge.
  - Theodore Roosevelt Highway (also known as Pacific Coast Highway and Route 1). (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes bridge at Rainbow Headlands, Piedras Blancas Light House, Salmon Creek Falls and Hearst Castle (in distance on top of hill).
  - Wreck of oil tanker Emidio. (Carton 8)
    Postcards of "General Petroleum Tanker Emidio," ship torpedoed by the Japanese off the Pacific Coast near Eureka, and then floated to Crescent City. December 1941.
  - Miscellaneous scenes in California. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Morro Rock; Point Lobos, Monterey; Point Arena coast; cross on Trinidad Head; landscape with Tule elk; beach along the Redwood Highway; Perrott Property in Humboldt County.
  - Miscellaneous scenes possibly in California. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes rivers and a road in the woods and coastal scenes.
  - Miscellaneous scenes outside of California. (Carton 8)
    Postcards. Includes Chetco River Bridge, Rainbow Rock and Bird Island near Brookings, Haystack Rock and cave in Oregon; Arches National Park, Canyonlands National Park and Capitol Reef National Park in Utah; Harvard Forest dioramas in Petersham, Massachusetts; Canterbury Shaker Village in New Hampshire.
- Series 5: Save the Redwoods League Officers., 1927-circa 2006; AX box 1, folders 21-25; B box 1, folder 16; NEG(gl) box 9.
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  Portraits of Save the Redwoods League officers and Members of Council. The bulk of the photographs are studio portraits.
  Formats include photographic prints and glass negatives. Prints were received framed, and removed from frames by Bancroft Library staff. Glass negatives are copy negatives. For additional portraits of Save the Redwoods League members, see: BANC PIC 1988.040--PIC.
  - Horace Albright. (Ax box 1, Folder 21)
    National Parks Service Director, 1929-1933; National Parks Service Assistant Director, 1917-1919; Save the Redwoods League Councilor, 1930-1987.
  - Katherine Anderton. (Ax box 1, Folder 21)
    Executive Director and Secretary Save the Redwoods League, 1991-2006.
  - Frederick Russell Burnham., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
  - Ralph W. Chaney. (Ax box 1, Folder 21)
    President of Save the Redwoods League, 1961-1971.
  - Ed Claassen. (Ax box 1, Folder 22)
    Councilor of Save the Redwoods League, Director of Save-the-Redwoods League, 1998-2008; President of Save-the-Redwoods League, 2002-2008.
  - William E. Colby., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
    California State Parks Commissioner.
  - Arthur E.Connick. (Ax box 1, Folder 22)
    Board of Directors, 1938-1951; Vice President, 1944-1951; Save the Redwoods League, 1951-1960.
  - John B. Dewitt. (Ax box 1, Folder 23)
    Secretary and Executive Director of Save the Redwoods League, 1971-1995.
  - Aubery Drury. (Ax box 1, Folder 23)
    Administrative Secretary of Save the Redwoods League, 1940-1959.
  - Newton Bishop Drury. (Ax box 1, Folder 23)
    Secretary of Save-the-Redwoods League, 1919-1940, 1959-1971; President of Save the Redwoods League, 1971-1976; Chairman of the Board, 1976-1978.
  - Newton Bishop Drury and Richard M. Leonard. (B box 1, Folder 16)
    Richard M. Leonard: Board of Directors, 1954-1980; Vice President of Save the Redwoods League, 1971-1975; President of Save-the-Redwoods League, 1975-1980; Chairman of the Board, 1980-1993.
  - Joseph D. Grant. (Ax box 1, Folder 23)
    Vice President and Chairman of the Board of Save the Redwoods League, 1920-1942.
  - Ruskin K. Hartley. (Ax box 1, Folder 24)
    Executive Director and Secretary Save the Redwoods League, 2006-.
  - Bruce S. Howard. (Ax box 1, Folder 24)
    Councilor Save the Redwoods League, 1963-; Board of Directors, 1965-2002; President of Save the Redwoods League, 1980-1995; Chairman of the Board, 1995-2002.
  - Duncan McDuffie. (Ax box 1, Folder 24)
    Board of Directors, 1925-1951; President of Save the Redwoods League 1944-1951.
  - Duncan McDuffie., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
  - Stephen T. Mather. (B box 1, Folder 16)
    NSP First Director, 1929-1933; Save the Redwoods League Board Member and Councilor, 1919-1926.
  - Henry W.O. Melrany., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
    State Parks Commissioner.
  - John C. Merriam. (Ax box 1, Folder 25)
    Founder and Councilor of Save the Redwoods League; President of Save the Redwoods League 1921-1944.
  - Frederick Law Olmsted., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
    Director of California State Park survey.
  - Richard C. Otter. (Ax box 1, Folder 25)
    Councilor of Save the Redwoods League, 1975-; Board of Directors, 1986-; Chairman of the Board, 2002-.
  - Earl Warren. (B box 1, Folder 16)
    Councilor of Save the Redwoods League, 1969-1974. Signed by Warren.
  - Ray Lyman Wilbur., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
  - C.C. (Clement Calhoun) Young., 1927 (Neggl box 9)
    Young signed the first California State Parks bill as governor.
- Series 6: Photographer Files., 1918-2006; carton 8; fALB v.11-14; NEG boxes 2, 4-9; NNEG boxes 1, 2, 5
  Arranged alphabetically by photographer, then by photographer code numbers or alphabetically by subject.
  Negatives, color transparencies, photographic prints and contact sheets for photographers Edward Ayer, Don Briggs, Carrie Grant, Evan Johnson, Howard King, Emerson Knight, Martin Litton and David Swanlund. Bulk are original negatives. Contact sheets or prints are available for most, but not all negatives. Unless otherwise noted, all negatives and contact sheets by these photographers fall in this series.
  Contact sheets and most negatives and transparencies were received from Save the Redwoods League in 3-ring binders. Some rehousing was done by Bancroft Library staff. Arrangement was left pretty much as received by the library.
  - Edward Ayer Collection., 1918-1922; fALB v.11; NNEG box 1
    Original negatives by photographer Edward Ayer, and modern contact sheets of the negatives.
    - Edward Ayer negatives A1 to A198., 1918-1922; 3 x 5 in. and smaller b&w negatives. (Nneg box 1)
      Parks and redwood groves that include the Eel River area, Bull Creek and Sempervirens Grove of Humboldt Redwoods State Park; Muir Woods; Big Basin; Santa Cruz Grove; Calaveras Grove; Wawona, Yosemite and Mariposa Grove; Montgomery Woods; and Pragg Crait Road. Also includes people traveling through redwoods forests in automobiles, log cabins, and Father Tree.
      Missing negatives A94-A99, A125-A129, A131-A134, A139-A141, A150-A153, A155-A156, A163, A167.
    - Contact sheets for negatives A1 to A198., 1918-1922 (Falb v.11)
      Includes an item list.
      For original prints see: Vertical Files -- Ayer, Edward E., collection.
  - Don Briggs Collection., 1985-1998; carton 8; NEG box 4
    Negatives and color transparencies, and matching contact sheets or prints by photographer Don Briggs.
    - Big Basin Redwoods State Park, negatives and transparencies., 6 4 x 5 in. color negatives; 9 2.25 x 2.75 in. color transparencies; 9 35mm color slides. (Neg box 4)
      Includes Holmes Rafael Grove and Nicholas Grove.
      Contact sheets not available for slides. Numbers start with DB 11485_.
    - Big Basin Redwoods State Park, contact sheets., 3 color contact sheets and 9 color prints. (Carton 8)
    - Highway 101 bypass (road construction), Prairie Creek, color slides., June 1985; 120 35mm color slides. (Neg box 4)
      No contact sheets.
    - Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park, negatives (J1 to J5)., March 1992; 5 sets of 2.25 x 2.75 in. color negatives. (Neg box 4)
      Includes Ernest L. and Lou R. Adams Grove, Mary Taft and Devereux Butcher Grove, National Tribute Grove, Amelia Earhart Memorial grove, and Mary Clayton Shaw Memorial Grove.
    - Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park, prints (J1 to J5)., March 1992; 5 sets of 4 x 5 in. color prints. (Carton 8)
    - Little Sur redwoods, negatives (DB 415851 to DB 415857)., 1985?; 7 sets of 2.25 x 2.75 in. color film. (Neg box 4)
    - Little Sur redwoods and canyon, negatives and transparencies. (DB 415858 to DB 415859, unnumbered)., 1985?; 2 sets of b&w negatives and 1 set of color transparencies, both 2.25 x 2.75 in. (Neg box 4)
    - Little Sur, contact sheets (DB 415851 to 415859, unnumbered)., 1985?; 9 sets of contact sheets. (Carton 8)
      Includes redwood trees and stream with waterfall.
      Contact sheets for negatives only. No contact sheets for transparencies.
    - Mendocino Headlands State Park and Sinkyone Wilderness, negatives and transparencies (DB A to DB I)., October 1986; 8 sets of color negatives and 1 set of color transparencies, both 2.25 x 2.75 in.; 2 color 35mm slides. (Neg box 4)
      Includes Big River, Sally Bell Grove, Sinkyone Grove, Wheeler Grove, Bear Harbor Barnum property and coast.
    - Mendocino Headlands State Park and Sinkyone Wilderness, prints (DB A to DB I)., October 1986; 9 sets of color contact sheets and 4 x 5 in. or smaller color prints. (Carton 8)
    - Miscellaneous slides and negatives., circa 1997-1998; 6 35mm slides, 15 2.25 x 2.75 in. color negatives (rolls K and 1L) and 2 color 4 x 5 in. copy negatives. (Neg box 4)
      Includes "Bad Burn," Sequoia National Park; coastal scenes and several unidentified images.
    - Miscellaneous contact sheets., 2 color contact sheets. (Carton 8)
      Contact sheet for roll 1L, roll K and of a bird flying.
    - Navarro River, negatives (DB 29851 to DB 29854)., February 9, 1985; 4 rolls of 2.25 x 2.75 in. color negatives. (Neg box 4)
    - Navarro River, contact sheets (DB 29851 to DB 29854)., February 9, 1985; 4 color contact sheets. (Carton 8)
    - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park [probably], transparencies (PC-1)., 1 strip of color transparencies. (Neg box 4)
    - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park [probably], contact sheets (PC-1)., 1 color contact sheet. (Carton 8)
      Some images lacking negatives.
    - Smith River, negatives and transparencies, January 1988; 4 rolls of color negatives and 1 roll of color transparencies, all 2.25 x 2.75 in.; 1 color 35mm slide, and 3 color 4 x 5 in. negatives (copy negatives?). (Neg box 4)
    - Smith River, contact sheets., January 1988; 6 color contact sheets. (Carton 8)
  - Carrie Grant Collection., NEG box 4
    Color slides by photographer Carrie Grant.
    - Carrie Grant slides., 98 35mm color slides. (Neg box 4)
      Includes Doulas fir and redwoods at Mill Creek and Sulphur Creek, Mattole North Fork watershed; Council Madrone, redwoods and Women's Federation Grove in Humboldt Redwoods State Park; Fern Canyon and James Irvine Trail in Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park; Damnation Creek in Del Norte Redwoods State Park.
      Slides only, no contact sheets.
  - Evan Johnson Collection., 1993-2006; carton 8; NEG boxes 2, 6
    Negatives and color transparencies, and matching contact sheets or prints by photographer Evan Johnson.